你们的游轮部门 有没有保留
In your cruise division by means of the keeping
影子日志
of shadow logs?
我相信当时我儿子在参与运营
I believe my son was across that operation.
翻译　水平有限的皮带断了
字　　幕　　侠
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
后期　Jason肖　特效　小布
ZIMUXIA.CN
看上去 很多文件已经被一个叫
It seems that a number of documents were signed out
校对　水平有限的皮带断了　时间轴　阿布
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
压制　Jason肖
格雷戈里·赫希的人注销了
by a Gregory Hirsch.
监制　水平有限的皮带断了
你认识这个人吗 万布斯甘斯先生
Is that someone known to you, Mr. Wambsgans?
ZIMUXIA.CN
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
不 不认识 对不起
No, no, sorry.
-"不认识"  -"不认识"吗 汤姆
‐No? ‐No, Tom?
我需要你去找主权财富基金
I need you to chase down the Sovereign Wealth money.
你们有没有能力把我们私有化
You guys have the muscle to take us private?
有
Yes.
你们能够来土耳其吗 来说服我
Could you come to Turkey? Pitch to me?
这些人是恐怖分子吗 还有
Are these terrorists? And,
我他妈的安保人员在哪 戴夫在哪
where's my fucking security guy? Where's Dave?
你们是另一个出价的目标
You're the target of another bid.
这难道不是问题吗
Isn't that a problem?
我不是想让这一切都围绕着我们
Not to make this all about us,
但是 他们会随时朝我们开枪吗
but are they going to shoot us at any point?
你要隐退的事 你一点也没告诉我
You told me nothing about you stepping aside.
你让我伤心了
You broke something here.
他们还有其他受害者
They have someone else for a victim.
我们能搞清楚她想要什么吗
Could we find out what she wants?
我不会进去的
I'm not going in.
我退出了 我不想成为这其中一份子
I'm out. I don't want to be part of this.
你认为我们渡过难关了吗
You think we're through?
股东大会是道坎 献血的时候到了
Not with the shareholders. Time for a blood sacrifice.
赫希先生 请起立
Mr. Hirsch, please rise.
请举起你的右手
Raise your right hand.
你是否能够向上帝发誓
Do you swear that the testimony
你将要在这个委员会作出的证言
you're about to give this committee
都是实话 是全部的事实 除此以外
is the truth, the whole truth, and nothing but the truth,
别无虚言
so help you God?
-我发誓  ‐请坐
‐I do. ‐Please take a seat.
艾维斯参议员 你的提问时间
Senator Eavis, it's your time.
格雷戈里·赫希 汤姆·万布斯甘斯的
Gregory Hirsch, executive assistant
行政助理 对吗
to Tom Wambsgans, correct?
是的
Yes.
是的 如果要这么说
Yes, if it is to be said.
你说什么
I'm sorry?
如果要这么说 那就这...那就是吧
If it is to be said, so it be... so it is.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
是的
Yes.
我只是想用肯定的方式回答
I merely wish to answer in the affirmative fashion.
你可以正常地和我们说话
You can speak to us normally.
好 不...谢谢 先生
Okay, no... Thank you, sir...
那我会的
So I shall.
比任何人都好
Be better than anyone else,
请允许我冒昧地声明
if I may be so bold as to declare.
-真的吗  ‐不 绝对是...
-Really? ‐No, absolutely...
那 你怎么看
So, what do you think?
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
我吗
Me?
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
如果你加上了卡罗丽娜 ...
If you added Karolina...
肯德尔
罗曼
小西
格丽
悉德
弗兰克
雷
卡尔
我
汤姆
这就是一份不错的领导阶层大餐
that's a decent bundle of leadership meat
可以对付鲨鱼群了
to feed the sharks.
狡猾的混球
Slippery cunt.
阴你的老板
Knife your boss?
你是个讨厌的混蛋 不是吗
You're a nasty bastard, aren't you?
嘿 是你自己问的 洛根
Hey, you asked, Logan.
他安全吗
Is he safe?
谁
Who?
罗曼
Roman.
我们给他找了医生 心理专家 干净的衣服 我们...
We got him a doctor, a shrink, fresh clothes, we...
我们把他需要的一切都给他准备好了
we got him everything he needs.
菲利普·莱顿
什么 不 不
What? No. No.
菲利普·莱顿
他妈的他现在怎么直接打电话给我了
How's he fucking calling me direct now?
-抱歉  ‐我他妈收到他的消息了
‐Sorry. ‐I got his fucking message!
-不  -我知道 我....
‐No. ‐I know. I....
很高兴和你联络 菲利普 不 你留这
Good to connect, Phillipe. No, you stay.
非常抱歉打扰你
I'm really sorry to bother you.
和大股东通话我还是有时间的
I've always got time for my big shareholders.
我正在去威尼斯见达图的路上
I'm on my way to see Datu in Venice.
他非常支持我 非常看好我
He's very supportive. Very bullish.
那很好
That's great.
但是我只是想确认一下 因为这是我们的立场
But I just wanted to check in, because here's our position,
我来总结一下
and I'm gonna summarize.
但是很显然 通常不会有股东支持一个
But obviously, no shareholder ordinarily would back
处于你目前这样的新闻困境的总裁
a CEO facing the press you're getting,
更不用说诉讼了
not to mention the litigation.
好吧 当然 这些不是...正常情况
Well, of course, these aren't... normal circumstances.
我是一个顽固的混蛋 但是我长远投资
I'm a tough bastard, but I invest.
我的意思是 你不能只是为了让该死驴跑几圈
I mean, you can't just flog the fucking donkey
就狠狠鞭打它 然后任由它死去
for a few more laps and then let it die.
没错...我们遭遇了风暴...
Yes... we've hit a squall...
但是已经结束了...
but it's over...
我正在安然度过危机...
I'm coming through...
我希望你能参加大会
and I hope you're joining the party.
太好了 但是问题是
Great, but here's the thing,
这话仅限于我们之间
and this is strictly between us,
我们需要一些掩护 你知道吗
but we need some cover, you know?
游轮的事情
The cruise stuff,
国会听证会 然后你儿子[被劫持]的事
congressional hearings, this kid today.
现在 我想在基本问题上投票给你
Now, I want to vote your ticket on the fundamentals.
我只是需要一些东西 证明你明白了
I just need something to show you get it.
嗯 我要处理...
Yeah, well, I gotta process...
你需要一个人选吗
you need a name?
格丽 卡尔 弗兰克
Gerri? Karl? Frank?
听着 这很难下决定 洛根
Look, this is a hard call to make, Logan,
但说实话 这事感觉太毒了...
but honestly, this thing feels so toxic...
我一直在打探情况 我们...
I've been taking soundings and we...
我们觉得应该是你
we feel that probably it should be you.
所以 是的 所以我觉得我应该保持联系
So, yeah. That's why I thought I should be in touch.
是的 对
Yeah. Right.
好吧 让我考虑一下
Well, let me think on that.
让我考虑一下
Let me think on that.
谢谢 洛根
Thanks, Logan.
这个决定不容易 很不容易
Not an easy call. Not an easy one.
不不不不 当然 当然 是的
No. No, no, no. Sure, sure. Yeah.
让我想想
Let me think.
再见
Bye.
我跟你说 格雷格可能进你的名单了
I tell you what. Greg might be talking himself onto your list.
要喝咖啡吗
Want a coffee?
我...我想...
I... I wanna...
继     承
第 二 季  第９集
本季终
你还好吗
You okay?
我只是觉得有点怪怪的
Guess I just felt a little bit weird, you know,
抛下一切过来
leaving it all.
这很完美
It's perfect.
开幕之后离开 再凯旋而归
Leave after opening night. Return in triumph.
是的 我不需要看评论
Yeah, I don't need to see the reviews,
你知道的 我不在乎
you know, I don't care.
没错啦 演出很精彩 谁会在乎...
Exactly. The play's brilliant. Who cares what some...
纽约时报的某个白人老狗写的评论呢
old white dude from The New York Times says?
脱鞋 宝贝
Shoes off, baby.
我的意思是 他们可能会喜欢演出 他们可能会爱死它
I mean, they might like it. They might love it.
是的
Yeah.
也许我们可以在一两个星期后看看评论
Maybe we can read the reviews in like a week or two.
当然 我的意思是 很明显 我必须在
Sure. I mean, obviously, I have to read them
米歇尔传给我综述之后阅读
after Michelle sends the roundup.
因为什么
Because?
因为我必须搞清楚我是不是在经济上破产了
Because I'll have to find out if I'm financially ruined.
-我会去的  -嘿
-I'll go. ‐Hey!
-第一位登船的  -嘿
‐First aboard. ‐Hey.
早起的鸟儿有最好的舱房住
Early worm catches the best cabin.
-嗨  -左转舵出海 右转舵回家
-Hi! ‐Port out. Starboard home.
欢迎来到我们的水上城市
Welcome to our city on the water.
这里就像威尼斯
lt's like Venice,
-但是闻起来很好  -谢谢
‐but it smells nice. ‐Thank you.
非常感谢你 看起来很可口
Thank you very much. Looks delicious.
嘿 那个是她吗
Hey. Is that her?
‐不 别问了 我会告诉你的  -好的
‐No, stop asking. I'll tell you. ‐Okay.
-你兴奋吗  -是啊
‐You excited? ‐ Yeah... Yeah!
我是...不 是的
I am... no, Yeah.
这个人...她肯定还想加入吗
Is this person... Is she still definitely into it?
是的 是的 放心 她已经准备好了
Yeah. Yeah. No, she's all primed.
-好的  -是的 我们视频聊过
‐Okay. ‐Yeah, we Facetimed.
-她很可爱  -好的
‐She's lovely. ‐Okay.
因为你似乎有点...
'Cause you seem a little...
不 不 太好了这很棒 这是...这是梦想 我的意思是...
No! No, it's great. It's great. It's... It's the dream. I mean...
没错 3P 太棒了
It is. Threesome. It's amazing.
-这是玛西娅改装的吗  -是的
‐Ew! Is this Marcia's refit? ‐Yeah.
这个设计就像是她和他断绝了关系一样
It's like her version of cutting up his ties.
不 因为我想让你看到这样安排的好处
No, because I want you to see the benefits of the arrangement.
没有 是的 谢谢 谢谢
No! Yes, thank you! Thank you.
这确实非常令人兴奋
And it's really, really exciting.
是的...但是你不觉得...
It's, ... But do you not think that with the...
家里人...
with the family...
到处都是 这样可能会有一点点...
all around, it might be a little...
我的意思是 我们为什么来这里 这是在干嘛
I mean, why are we here? What is this?
好吧 想法是来一个家庭小假期
Well, idea was a family mini break.
听证会之后 股东会之前 大家碰个头
Post‐Congress, pre‐shareholder meet. You know.
亲密的家人 玩玩充气艇 喝点香槟
Like, close family, and inflatables, and mimosas,
然后还有首席财务官和法律总顾问参与
and the CFO, and the general counsel.
是的 你知道的 没有首席财务官
Yeah, you know, vacation's not a vacation
假期就算不上是假期
without the chief financial officer.
是的
Yeah.
我一直在想 我希望我对参议员说的话
Like, I just keep thinking about things I wish I said
我差点希望
to the senators. Like, I almost wish
我用这样的话来开始 "没有女人受辱 没有人哭泣"
I just started out with, like, "No woman, no cry."
比如 如果我用 "没有女人受辱 没有人哭泣”
Like, what if I said, "No woman, no cry"
-来回答每个问题会怎么样  -对
‐to every single question? ‐Right.
或者 比如"我为了表示敬意自愿出席"
Or, like, "I volunteer as tribute."
你怎么看 你喜欢吗
What do you think? You like it?
-不 这...  -就一个"嗯哼"吗
‐No, it's...  ‐Just "uh huh"?
不 不...不 很好
No, n... No, it's nice.
我觉得这不止值一个"嗯哼”
I feel like it's a little more than "uh huh".
你...你有预订吗
You... You have, reservations?
没有 伙...不 这很好...我的意思是 这是一艘非常不错的船
No, du... No, it's great... I mean, it's a very nice ship.
绝对是一艘大船...
It's definitely a big ship...
好吧 好吧 玛西娅把它改装了
All right, well, Marcia had it refitted
所以你得脱鞋
so you gotta take your shoes off.
脱鞋吗 ...我可能不会
Shoes off?...I might not.
不 这是上游艇的唯一规则 伙计
No. That's the one rule on these things, man.
柚木甲板 不能穿鞋
Teak deck, no shoes.
如果...如果脚趾甲
What if... What if your toenails
看上去很不赏心悦目 怎么办
are not all that aesthetically pleasing?
起航了 没得变了 兄弟
Sails out, nails out, bro.
嘿 显然...你听说过这个吗
Hey, apparently... Have you heard this?
-什么  ‐我现在是GIF动画
‐What? ‐I'm a GIF now!
一个"康粉"发出来的
One of the Conheads sent it in.
-我是个表情包了  -你是表情包
‐I'm a meme. ‐You're a meme?
是的 我变成表情包了
Yeah. I got memed.!
"康粉"们爱死这个了
The Conheads are loving this.
你知道吗 这真的非常非常正面
You know, this is really all very, very positive.
-好的 主矿脉  -什么
‐Okay. Mother lode. ‐What?
公关部的米歇尔刚传过来一大堆东西
Full bundle just came in from PR Michelle.
天哪 我受不了了 好吧 直接说吧
God, I can't bear it. Okay, go ahead.
我就看你脸上的表情 我就用这种方式来解读
I'll just look at your face and I'll get them that way.
-是吗  -是的
-Yeah? ‐Yeah.
是好评吗 你读到好评了吗
Is that goodie? Did you read a goodie?
他妈的 就告诉我吧 快点 评论怎么样
Fuck it! Just tell me. Come on. How are they?
各种都有
A mixture.
好吧 好吧 读一条给我听 读一条好的给我听
Okay, well, read me one. Read me one good one.
-好吧 好吧  -嗯
‐Okay. Okay. ‐Right.
好吧 泰晤士报怎么说
Well, what did The Times say?
宝贝 你知道吗 不如我们先玩开心
Baby, you know what? Let's just have a good time,
然后 等我们准备大笑时...
and then, you know, when we're ready for a laugh...
-来 让我看看  ‐你知道吗 不如我们...
‐Come on, let me take a look. ‐You know, why don't we just....
给我...那个 松手
Just give me... the thing. Just stop.
-在哪里...在哪里   -是...不 在这里
‐Where... Where is it? ‐lt's... No. Here.
只管...只管忽略标题 好吗
Just... Just ignore the headline, okay?
不用理会 因为...
Disregard that because...
他们来了 亚洲英雄 小亚细亚
Here they are, the heroes of Asia. Asia Minor!
土耳其的狮子们
The lions of Turkey!
怒吼吧 你好
Roar. Hi.
‐见到你很高兴 伙计  ‐你看起来糟透了
‐Good to see you, man. ‐You look like shit.
‐欢迎回来 伙计  -嗯
‐Welcome back, man. ‐Yup.
像奥德修斯一样归来 你骑羊了吗[出自奥德修斯斗独眼巨人的神话]
Back like Odysseus. Did you ride out on sheep?
嗯 我听说你一个人打垮了一支军队 兄弟
Yeah, I heard you took down an army alone, bro.
如果你不是已经这么糟糕了
That would have been really traumatizing
那会是真正的精神创伤
if you weren't already so fucked up.
你为了逃出来拍了谁的马屁
Who'd you suck off to get out?
你是住在四季酒店 对吧
You were staying at a Four Seasons, right?
那你是怎么逃脱的 你是不是....
So how did you escape? Did you....
你是不是用凯撒沙拉制作了滑翔机
Did you, like, build a glider ‐out of a Caesar salad?
你知道吗...真的他妈的很吓人的
You know what?...It was actually fucking scary,
我们以为他们会杀了我们 但是 我们没事了
and we thought that they might kill us, but yeah.
"凯撒沙拉"
"Caesar salad."
-对不起 老弟 说真的  ‐不 没关系
‐Sorry, dude. Seriously. ‐No, it's all right.
嗯 你知道吗 他们"强暴"了我一点点
Yeah, yeah. You know, they raped me a little,
但我不是英雄
but I'm no hero.
括号 而是个了不起的英雄
Parentheses, I'm an incredible hero.
-对不起 老哥  -嗯 没关系....
‐Sorry, bro. ‐Yeah. It's fine....
没关系 我...很累 总之 真好笑
It's fine. I'm... tired, or whatever. It was funny.
卡尔差点要在桶里拉屎了 我已经拍在手机里了
Karl almost shat in a bucket, and I have it on my phone,
所以 我们以后多得是机会羞辱他
so we will fully humiliate him later.
好 是的 太好了 是的 这样做吧 那样...
Good. Yeah, excellent. Yeah, do that. That's...
-那样很好  ‐我会告诉你一件事
‐That'll be great. ‐I will tell you one thing.
我他妈想喝一瓶那边的冻啤酒
I could use one of those fucking cold beers.
-好的  -好的
-Yeah. ‐ Okay.
那 从商业角度来看 一切进展如何
So, how'd it all go, business wise?
-还是说已经忘了这事  ‐你 ...
‐Or did that get forgotten? ‐Y...
对此我们不能说太多
We can't say too much about that.
好吧 有前途
Okay, promising.
好吧 这是机密 但是小伙子干得不错
Well, it's confidential, but the kid did good.
-嘿 这太棒了  -O鸡巴K了
-Hey. That's fantastic. ‐Okie‐doke.
很好棒
Nice.
-是的 谢谢 谢谢  -很高兴你没事
‐Yeah. Thanks. Thank you. ‐Glad you're okay.
罗曼 你好吗 老弟
Rome, how you doin', buddy?
-你没事吧  -好极了
‐You good? ‐Swell.
那 继续说 你还没告诉我华盛顿的情况呢
So, go on. You haven't told me yet. How was DC?
什么 听证会吗
What, the hearings?
是的 真他妈的真实
Yeah. Pretty fucking real.
嗯 我看了 你做得不错
Yeah. I watched. You did good.
好吧 怎么了
Okay. What?
继续说  "对于...对于一个瘾君子来说...对于一个白痴瘾君子来说"
Go on. "F... For a crack head... moron on crack."
没有
No.
不 你做得不错
No, you did okay.
是的 肯搞定了
Yeah, Ken nailed it.
-谢谢  -肯做得很棒
-Thanks. ‐ Ken did great.
汤姆倒是吓得大便失禁
It was Tom who farted in his shit.
你知道 很多人都说我是炮灰[直译是死猫]
You know, a lot of people are saying I was deadcatting.
他们这么说吗 真的吗
They saying that? Really?
"炮灰" 你从没听说过吗
"Deadcat." You never heard of that?
-没有  -嗯...
-No. ‐Well...
桌子上的炮灰
Dead cat on the table.
突然 每个人都在看着那个炮灰
Suddenly, everyone's looking at the dead cat,
而不是谈论...谈论你的父亲
and not talking... talking about your dad.
对 不 不 你吸引了...
Right. No, no, you drew...
-你吸引了火力 是的  -谢谢
‐you drew the fire. Yeah. ‐Thank you.
那 有什么想法呢 瑞亚出局了 对吧
So, what's the thinking? Rhea's out, right?
瑞亚出局了
Rhea's out.
消失了 但是 她同意在股东大会之前
Melted. But she's agreed to not say anything publicly
不公开发表任何言论 所以...
until after the shareholder meeting, so...
好吧 那 接替瑞亚方面...
Okay, so, then instead of Rhea...
谁的大毛脚适合这双玻璃拖鞋
whose big, hairy foot's gonna fit in the glass slipper?
华盛顿·肯吗
Washington Ken?
我吗...不 不是
Me?...No. Nope.
我的意思是 罗曼
I mean, Rome.
-如果你把金鸡带回家了 就是你的了  -也许吧
‐lf you brought the goose home. ‐  Maybe.
任何人都有可能 我的意思是 格雷格为什么在这里
Could be anybody. I mean, why is Greg here?
我总是问这个问题
I always ask that question.
嘿 格雷格 你准备好上位了吗
Hey, Greg. You ready to step up?
他们觉得这是一种真菌
It's a fungus, they think.
良性真菌
Benign fungus.
很适合做你的回忆录标题
Great title for your memoir.
-你说什么  -良性真菌
‐What's that? ‐ A Benign Fungus.
是她吗
That her?
-是的  -是吗
‐Yeah. ‐Yes?
她觉得有点恶心
She's grossed out a little.
我真的想过...
I did think...
当我以为 你知道的 他们会...
when I thought, you know, they were gonna...
挖出我的内脏
vacuum out my innards
然后用混凝土或其他东西填充我...
and fill me with concrete or something...
听着 如果我们经历了这样的事...
Look, if we come through this...
有没有什么话题...
is there a thing where we like...
是我们可以...
talk to each other about stuff...
正常交流的
normally?
你想正常交流吗
You wanna talk to each other normally?
好的
Okay.
-你的意思是...谈谈大篓子吗  - 好的
‐ You mean... talk about the big shit? ‐ Okay.
是的 我们可以谈谈大篓子
Yeah, we can talk about the big shit.
我们可以谈谈...
We can talk about...
我们的感受
our feelings.
我怎么成了这里的成年人了
How am I the mature one here?
我们没有任何感受
We don't have any feelings,
你在说什么啊
what are you talking about?
这样能帮到谁呢
Who is this helping?
好了 情绪化的武装直升机来了
Okay. Emotional gunship incoming.
是的 发出求救信号
Yeah, send out the distress signal.
我们受到攻击
We're under attack.
-嘿 欢迎  - 嘿 老爸
-Hey! Welcome. ‐ Hey, Dad!
嗨 嗨嗨嗨 你好
Hi! Hi, hi, hi. Hi.
-嘿 嘿  - 他来了
‐Hey. Hey. ‐ Here he is.
嘿
Hey!
罗曼 莱尔德 卡尔 谈正事
Roman. Laird. Karl. Business.
那...
So...
-你还好吗  -是的
‐are you okay? ‐  Yeah.
‐我听说事情变得有点戏剧  -是的 我们很好
‐I heard it got a bit tasty. ‐yeah. We're fine.
我有过更糟糕的酒店经历
I've had worse experiences at hotels.
我以前住过万豪
I once stayed at a Marriott.
他们照顾你了吗 我跟白宫说了
They look after you? I spoke to the White House.
是的 他们说他们派了军舰 但是我不知道
Yeah, they said they sent a warship, but I don't know,
我觉得军舰早就在那里了
I think it was already there.
然后大使带我们出去吃了顿垃圾午餐
Then the ambassador took us out for a shitty lunch
中情局的一个家伙用红酒猛灌我们[waterboard是水刑的意思]
and someone from the agency gave us the ol' Merlot waterboard.
那...关于资金的事
So... on the money.
情况怎么样
What's the situation?
嗯 小伙子做得很好
Well, the kid did great.
罗伊先生 我觉得 你可以把你的公司私有化
I think, Mr. Roy, you can take your firm private.
爱德华和他父亲在主权财富上的权力
Eduard and his father have titular responsibility
有名无实
for the sovereign wealth,
但是总统女儿的丈夫 扎纳尔
but the president's daughter's husband, Zeynal,
现在是关键人物
is the key guy now,
而罗曼...大满贯扣篮
and Roman... slam dunked it.
好吧 很明显爱德华已经靠边站了
Well, it was clear that Eduard was getting sidelined,
然后扎纳尔搞清楚了我们是什么人
and then Zeynal figured out who we were.
我以为我们会被他妈的...
I thought we were gonna get taken for a fucking...
电锯大卸八块 结果...不是
chainsaw massage, but... no.
我们有一个小时 努力地推销 然后 没错 他们说想加入
We got an hour, pitched hard, and yeah, they say they want in.
太谦虚了 他大获全胜
Too modest; he killed.
你应该经常拿枪指着他的脑袋逼逼他
You should put a gun to his head more often.
阿塞拜疆人说他们可以投入100亿
The Azeris say they can put in ten bil.
莱尔德可以把其余的放在一起
Laird can put together the rest,
资金撤出时间是六年
and the exit horizon's like six years.
你...喜欢这样 杰米
And you... like it, Jaime?
是的 嗯 我喜欢
Yeah. Yeah, I like it.
我觉得他们可以快速动起来 而且...
I think they can move fast and...
这种情况都和人际关系有关
this sort of situation's all about relationships.
好吧 那...那太好了
Well, that's... that's great.
真是太棒了
That's fucking fantastic.
你可以告诉你那些惊慌失措的股东们 可以鸣笛庆贺了
You can tell your spooked shareholders to go whistle.
我必须说一件事 爸
I do have to say one thing, Dad.
罗曼 我们很好
Roman, we're good.
我的意思是...
I mean...
我确实和扎纳尔进行了很好的交谈
I did have a good conversation with Zeynal,
他说 用他的嘴巴说的
and he said, with his mouth,
他想加入 那样很棒
that he wanted in and that's all great.
但是如果我们对此真的很认真
But if this is really serious for us,
我想我确实不得不说 这感觉像是...
I think I actually do have to say it feels like it is...
可能是扯谈
probably horse shit.
别这样 别这样 小伙子
Come, come, kiddo.
他们古里古怪的
They were flaky.
当时发生了很多烂事
There was a lot of shit going on.
罗曼...
Roman...
他们想重新平衡他们的投资组合
they want to rebalance their portfolio.
由于各种地缘政治的原因
For a variety of geopolitical reasons,
他们的资金大量集中在欧洲
they're heavily European‐focused
他想往西半球倾斜
and he wants to tilt Western Hemisphere.
这很合逻辑 我知道那是...很多钱
It's very logical. I know that it's... it's a lot of money
可能会多到让人害怕 但是这...这说得通
and that can be scary, but it... it makes sense.
好吧 很抱歉让我漂亮的小脑袋不安了
Well, sorry for worrying my pretty, little head,
但是如果他们要重新平衡自己的投资组合
but if they're rebalancing their portfolio,
用一笔一百亿的巨额交易来平衡 而不是分散到各领域投资
it's fucking insane to do it with one ten‐bil mega‐deal
这真是他妈的疯了
rather than a ton spread across different sectors.
他们同意了 罗曼
They said yes, Roman.
好吧 当然 他们同意了
Well, sure, they said yes.
也许是真实的 也许吧
And maybe it's real. Maybe.
有百分之十到二十的机会
There's a ten to 20 percent chance
你能从中赚到1亿
that you make what, like, 100 million here?
这很令人兴奋 但是如果我们失手了
That's very exciting. But if we miss,
我们可能会被干死 因为消息会传出去
we could be fucked, because it gets out
说我们盯着这种钱
we're looking at this kind of money,
这在政治上会非常可怕
it's going to be politically horrible.
如果我们失败了...
If we fail...
我们会输掉代理权投票 我们就死了 对吧
we lose the proxy vote and we die. Right?
如果投票支持率跌到一半...
If it falls halfway through...
我们就奄奄一息了
it's terminal.
但是如果行得通 你一跳就自由了
But if it works, one bound and you're free.
儿子
Son?
爸 我必须承认
Dad, I have to say,
我刚刚瞎扯了一点
I've done a little bullshitting in my time.
他是个瘾君子 满口胡扯 凌晨三点喝酒
He was a cokey, bullshit, 3:00 a. M. Scotch
一直喝到天亮 他根本没有露面
and see‐you‐in‐the‐morning man. He ain't showing up.
莱尔德 他妈的诚实点
Laird, be fucking honest.
他在向卡尔抱怨 他的人脉都快死了
He was bleating to Karl. His contacts are all dying,
他作为高级顾问会被排挤到一边
and he's gonna get shoved aside as the senior advisor
除非他今年能赚大钱
unless he pulls major gravy this year.
我甚至不知道该说什么
I don't even know what to say to that.
那就什么也别说
Then don't say anything.
爸 我希望那是真的 我真的很他妈的希望 但是...
Dad, I wish it was real. I really fucking do, but...
卡尔
Karl.
你不能指望这个 现在不能
You can't lean on this. Not now.
嗯 但是如果你没搞定这个 你的另一个选择是什么
Yeah, but if you don't get this, your other option is what?
对不起 杰米 继续胡扯 继续瞎编
I'm sorry, Jaime. Keep exploring, keep talking,
但我不能把筹码压在不牢靠的事情上
but I cannot pile my chips on something that isn't solid.
那真是太棒了
That is just excellent.
你太离谱了 罗曼
You are way off, Roman.
谢谢你 卡尔
And thank you, Karl.
我希望你能享受国王的恩宠
I hope you enjoy the king's favors,
因为你知道 如果不私有化
because you know what you're looking at
会是什么结局
if you don't go private.
‐莱尔德…  ‐得有人为此付出代价
‐Laird... ‐Someone has to pay the price.
也许是你 罗曼 或者你的某个兄弟姐妹
Maybe you, Roman, or maybe one of your siblings.
我想你会有一段毁掉生活的快乐时光 证券交易委员会 ...
I suppose you'll have a fun little time ruining a life. SEC...
司法部 ...外国和腐败行为
DOJ... Foreign and Corrupt Practices.
有人会被扔下热气球
Someone's getting tossed out of the balloon
有人可能会入狱
and someone is likely going to jail.
所以 晚安 女士们
So, goodnight, ladies.
晚安...亲爱的女士们
Goodnight... sweet ladies.
还有祝你好运
And good luck.
嘿
Hey.
怎么样了
How'd that go?
我觉得也许不是解决方案
I think maybe not the solution.
那 情况会变得...
So, it's gonna get...
波涛起伏
choppy.
我他妈的不敢相信
I can't fucking believe it.
我
Me?
我从没做过任何真实的事
I never did anything really.
一个好天主教小伙子 一个甚至在他的妻子面前
A good Catholic lad who couldn't even take his undershirt off
都不肯脱汗衫的人
in front of his wife.
他的前妻 不管她是他妈的什么东西
His ex‐wife, whatever the fuck she is.
我
Me.
其他所有人都像一群该死的流浪狗
All the rest behave like a pack of fucking stray dogs.
不
No.
你知道吗 斯图威在希腊
You know, Stewy's in Greece.
不 不 不 不 不 不 不 不 儿子 不 我...
No, no, no, no, no, no. No. No. No, son. No. No, I...
我他妈的去过那里了
Fucking been there.
我操
Shit!
好吧 好吧 让开
Okay, okay. Get out of the way!
好了
Okay.
我不知道自己要不要玩
I don't know if I want to.
嘿
Hey.
那...我听说...
So... I hear...
-私有化没戏了 对吧  -好了 准备好了吗
‐private's off, right? ‐Okay! Ready?
只是最后不信任他们
Just didn't trust them in the end.
我无法解释原因
I can't explain why.
因为你有点种族主义吗
'Cause you're a bit racist?
我不这么觉得 但是总有这种可能性
I didn't think so, but there's always that possibility.
这样很吓人 非常非常吓人
It's bad. It's very, very bad.
嘿 格雷格 你在喝什么
Hey, Greg. What are you drinking?
这是...我不确定 是...是玫红酒
This is... I'm not sure. It's a... It's a rosé.
这不是我的最爱
It's not my favorite.
你现在都有最爱的香槟了啊
You got a favorite champagne now.
好吧...一不小心又被你发现了
Well... you can't help noticing.
没关系 我会喝的 只不过这不是我的最爱
It's fine. I'll drink it. It's just not my favorite.
好吧 你最好喝光 老弟 因为...
Well, you better drink up, brother, because...
如果你最终带着罐头乘船旅行
if you end up carrying the can for cruises,
那你最后会回到从碟子里喝牛奶的状态
you'll be back to drinking milk from a saucer.
我们要私有化了
We're going private.
-交易没戏了  -什么
‐Deal's off. ‐What?
会有一个人当炮灰
There's gonna be a head on a spike.
嘿 老爸
Hey, Pa.
问一个简短的 不是大问题的问题
A quick one, not a biggie.
我在评论方面需要一些帮助
I need some help on reviews.
-演出吗  -是的
‐The play? ‐Yeah.
只是赞扬一下
Just a spritz of praise.
一些报纸头条
Some poster toppings.
纪事报或者先驱报...
The Chronicle or The Herald, just...
你能稍微带点节奏吗
could you lean a little bit?
你知道 类似...不是这样的 而是类似 比如
You know, something like... Not this, but something like,
"值得购票观看”
"Kill for a ticket,"
或者"季度戏剧盛事"
or "The theatrical event of the season."
我不喜欢对我的人带节奏
I do not like to lean on my people.
得了吧
Come on.
我的意思是 你在粮食补贴问题上
I mean, you brought down a Canadian government
搞垮了加拿大政府 但是不能给我安排一个
over grain subsidies, you can't give me
‐他妈的轻而易举的评论  -嘿 嘿 淡定
‐one fucking lousy review? ‐Hey. Hey, easy!
我听说你浪费了50万买了一根假的拿破仑的鸡巴
I hear you jizzed 500K on a fake Napoleon dick.
这不相关 听着 爸 我...我真的很受伤
That's irrelevant. Look, Pa, I'm... I'm actually hurtin' here.
一周花50万 我有奥斯特里茨[拿破仑在此大胜俄国和奥地利]
It's a half a mil a week. I've got Austerlitz,
我参加了竞选 但我的流动资金不足
I've got my campaign, and I'm not super liquid,
所以我只是...
so I'm just...
我只是想知道 我是不是可以向你...
I'm just wondering if I could hit you for like...
借个...小小的一个亿
like... a little 100 mil.
‐小小的一个亿  -是的
‐A little 100 mil? ‐Yeah.
好吧 也许吧 也许
Well, you know, maybe. Maybe.
但是你必须退出竞选
But you have to quit your campaign.
什么...爸 不 我有整个团队
Wha... Pa, no. I got a whole team.
只是在经济上表明判断合理 我是出于好心
Just to financially indicate sound judgment, good intentions.
我有浮动政策 我有民调 我有康粉...
I'm floating policy, I got feelers, I got the Conheads....
这是一个瞎扯谈的白日梦
It's a horseshit pipe dream.
每个人都觉得你是个笑话
Everybody thinks you're a joke.
而且你他妈的让我很尴尬
And you're fucking embarrassing me.
嗯 说得对
Right. Right.
感谢你坦诚相告
Thanks for your honesty.
退出竞选 我们再深入研究
Pull the plug and we'll get into it all.
但是现在 我要炸更大的鱼了
But now, I got bigger fish to fry.
-...不错 很好  ‐那 嘿 大家听着
-...Nice. Lovely. ‐So, hey, listen up.
我只是想说 这里有很多传言
I just wanted to say there are a lot of whispers going around,
但是今晚我不会宣布是谁来背锅
but I'm not going to make an announcement tonight.
我想做最好的事情 最体面的事情
I wanna do the best thing, the most decent thing,
所以 明天 我们将进行讨论
so, tomorrow, we'll get into a discussion
关于我们的失误和...
about our missteps and...
我们应该如何表达对世界上其他地方的深切歉意
how we can indicate how sorry we are to the rest of the world.
好吗 我们在座的都是朋友 对吧
Okay? We're all pals here. Right?
所以...今晚 好好喝一杯
So... tonight, drink up.
明天 我们会解决的
And tomorrow, we'll figure it out.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
看来 有人被炒了
So, someone's getting shitcanned.
我们开始派对吧
Let's get the party started.
喂 威拉
So, Willa,
-演出怎么样  -滚蛋
‐how's the play going? ‐Fuck off!
你感觉怎么样
How are you feelin'?
生病 焦虑
Sick, anxious.
你觉得他为什么这样做
Why is he doing it like this do you think?
你什​​么意思
How do you mean?
"我们在座的都是朋友"
"We're all pals here."
"我们讨论一下" 表现得好像他突然想听我们的观点
"Let's have a discussion." Like he suddenly wants our views
因为他喜欢听劝一样
'cause he loves advice.
他正在进行一场审判秀
He's running a show trial.
让整个政治局签署死刑令
You get the whole politburo to sign the death warrant,
然后我们所有人的手上都会沾满鲜血
then all our hands are bathed with blood.
很好很可爱
That's nice and lovely.
没有接待人员 死亡巡游吗
No reception. Death cruise?
你觉得是谁
Who are you thinking?
-你知道吗  -知道什么
‐You know what? ‐What?
弗兰克
Frank!
我听说会是你
I hear it's gonna be you.
是的 去你的
Yeah, screw you.
‐你听到什么消息了  ‐我来登记
‐What have you heard? ‐  I got a book going.
想在自己身上下一百万的注吗
Want to put a million on yourself?
我给你四比一的赔率
I'll give you four‐to‐one odds.
让自己在回家的路上甜蜜翻番
Make that ride home much sweeter.
好吧 我们...到底在说什么
Okay, are we... What exactly are we hearing here?
我听说是弗兰克[当炮灰]
I'm hearing Frank.
是的
Yeah.
-你什么意思  -他在胡说八道
-What do you mean? -He's bullshitting.
好吧 有点道理
Well, it's plausible.
有点道理 选你才有点道理
It's plausible. You're plausible.
嘿 我没说我不可能
Hey, I didn't say I wasn't.
不 你实际上是主要候选人 六比一的赔率
No, you're actually a prime candidate. Six‐to‐one.
这个...这个...太可怕了 罗曼 我们是实实在在的人
This... This... This is horrible. Roman, we're real people.
而你不是
You are not.
你声称自己实实在在 但是看看你 看看你
You claim to be real, but look at ya. Look at ya!
墨镜很酷 姐们 ....
Cool shades, bro. ....
你的短裤颜色和你的玫红酒很称
Your shorts match your rosé.
-是计划好的还是只是...  -好了 我来了
-Was that planned or just a... Yeah. ‐All right. I'm coming.
所以
So.
你打算什么时候问
When were you gonna ask?
娜奥米吗 我...我问了 我...我让凯莉发短信给...
Naomi? I... I did. I... I asked Kerry to send word to...
没有发吗
No?
我是说 是的 我...
I mean, yeah. I...
我喜欢她 爸爸
I like her, Dad.
还有...
And...
我觉得这可能是一个艰难的周末 而且...
thought it could be a rough weekend and...
我知道我有过不幸的婚史 但是...
I know there's history, but...
我的意思是 她...她...
I mean, she's... she's...
对我来说是个很好的选择 爸爸
kind of a good one for me, Dad.
对
Right.
我消息不灵通
I wasn't properly informed.
我只是不确定我们有足够的心理准备
And I'm just not sure we have enough provisions.
我在华盛顿的时候 发现她对我很支持...
I found her a great support in DC...
我什么事都需要隐私
I need privacy for everything.
-嗯 她明白的  ‐所有的一切
‐Yeah, she gets it. ‐For everything.
是的 我知道 她会...她会回避的
Yeah, I know. She'll... She'll stay out of the way.
我...我的意思是 她很棒 我的意思是...
I... I mean, she's great. I mean...
我只是不想让你再吸毒了
I just don't want you fucked on drugs.
而她和你一起吸毒 不是吗
And she's part of it. Isn't she?
我应该...去敲门然后邀请她过来吗
Should I... do the knock and invite her up?
好吧 我...
Well, I...
我的意思是 是吗 好啊
I mean, right? Yeah?
-好的  -好的
‐Okay. ‐Okay.
我有一种...
There is kind of...
有一种死刑判决的氛围 但是...是的 很好
kind of death‐sentence vibes, but... yeah. It's good.
好的
Okay.
我很好奇...我很好奇我们是不是可以做点什么
I wonder... I wonder if there is something we could do.
我不知道我是不是有精力来面对这种淫乱
I don't know if I have the vim for the full dirty.
所以 我们...
So, we...
但是我们可以...
But we could...
什么
What?
来吧 你可以说出来
Come on, you can say.
我可以围观吗
Could I watch?
-我的意思是...  -是的
‐I mean... ‐Yeah!
或者这样更好 她可以围观我们吗
Or even better. Could she watch us?
是的 她可以...
Yeah. She could...
‐她...她可以围观我们  -嗯
‐She... She could watch us. ‐Yeah.
‐有点性感吧  ‐我的意思是 我必须...
‐Kind of sexy? ‐I mean, I would have to...
看看她是不是...但是
see if she's... But it's...
-是的 就像 我...我的意思是...  -好
‐Yeah. Like, I... I mean... ‐Fine.
我敢肯定我会 因为这太让人性奋了
I'm sure I will, 'cause it's so hot.
但是有可能...
But there is a chance...
我只是提个健康警告 有可能
Just a health warning. There's a chance
我可能...我可能无法...
that I might... I might not be able to...
参与
perform.
-因为我无法...我不知道  -汤姆 不
‐Because I can't... I don't know. ‐Tom, no.
可能是因为我以前没在大庭广众表演过
Probably because I haven't done a stadium gig before.
亲爱的 你会没事的
Honey, you'll be fine.
我们会帮你的
We'll help you.
或者她不能围观 我们可以让她待在浴室里
Or she could not watch. We could put her in the bathroom
她可以透过钥匙孔看
and she could look through the keyhole.
汤姆 我觉得你正在把我们的3P变成2P
Tom, I feel like you're turning our threesome into a twosome.
我只是...对不起 对不起 亲爱的 我不...我...
I just... I'm sorry. I'm sorry, honey. I just don't... I've...
我不知道怎么...
I don't know how...
我今晚没有那种下流的感觉
I don't feel that naughty tonight.
好的 没关系
Okay. That's fine.
-嗯 我只是以为我们可以...  -抱歉
‐Yeah, I just thought we could... ‐Sorry.
-没事 不不不 我以为会...  -不 是...
‐No. No, no, no. I thought it would be something... ‐No, it's...
做一些让我们兴奋的事情
that we could do that would be exciting for us.
-不 是…  -没关系
‐No, it's... ‐That's okay.
没事 因为我还得去和爸爸谈谈
It's good, 'cause I have to go and talk to Dad anyway
关于明天的事 所以...
about tomorrow, so...
嘿 她来了吗
Hey. Did she come?
跟我一起走
Come with me.
我...我只是...
I... I just...
这很重要
It's a big time.
是的 不 当然
Yeah, no, of course.
不 拜托 这...这件事...
Nay, come on. This... This is like...
客观上是一场危机
objectively a crisis.
对不起 真的
I'm sorry. I am.
他爱我 他...他...他...他确实
He loves me. He... He... He... He does,
我觉得这只是一种错误的爱的表达方式
I think it's just a wrong kind of love expression.
是的 肯 他爱破碎的你
Yeah. Ken, he loves the broken you.
那才是他爱的
That's what he loves.
也许我们会再见的
Maybe I'll meet you there.
也许吧
Maybe.
嗨
Hi.
-嗨  -早上好 先生
‐Hi. ‐Good morning, sir.
我可以给你倒点什么喝的吗
May I offer you something to drink?
给我一整瓶勃艮第红酒
I will take a full bottle of Burgundy.
-没问题  -拜托了 谢谢
-Certainly. ‐Please. Thank you.
早餐喝这么多吗 老康
For breakfast, Con?
好吧 是的 早餐喝 为什么不可以
Well, yes, for breakfast. Why not?
好吧...
All right...
我们游个泳或者放松放松 然后...我们开聊
Let's have a swim or relax, and then... we can chat.
我不知道我个人
I don't know how relaxing a time
能够有多放松 但是 当然
I'm personally going to be able to have, but sure.
好吧 反正不是你 老弟 所以你可以放松
Well, it's not gonna be you, man, so you can chill.
是的 我知道 但是我不知道他在想什么
Yeah, I know, but I don't know what he has in mind.
-那你在想什么  -够了 好吗
-What do you have in mind? ‐Enough. Okay?
我们团结在一起
We stick together.
大多数东西都不存在
Most things don't exist.
福特汽车公司差点就不存在了
The Ford Motor Company hardly exists.
这只是一种节省时间的表达方式
It's just a time‐saving expression
为了一堆经济利益
for a collection of financial interests.
但是...这个存在 因为...
But... this exists, because...
-"家庭"  -这是一个家庭
‐ "Family." ‐ it's a family.
我们是一家人
We are a family.
所以...我觉得...
So... I think...
我觉得显而易见的选择...
I think the obvious choice...
是我
is me.
所以 这就是我要宣布的内容
So, that's what I'd like to announce.
不 不行 不能是你
No. No, you can't.
好吧 你知道吗 我可能没有责任
Well, you know, I may not be responsible,
但责任总得有人承担
but the buck has to stop somewhere.
-不  -不 绝对不行 绝对不行
-No. ‐ No, never. Never.
不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no.
不能在代理权争夺战的时候牺牲你
Not in the middle of a proxy fight.
我觉得这样不行 爸 我觉得这样不行 不行
I don't think so, Dad. I don't think so. No.
我的意思是 也许...也许列个时间表
I mean, maybe a... maybe a timetable,
但直接让你担责行不通
but actually go doesn't work.
等到大家发现瑞亚没有加入公司的时候
When people find Rhea isn't coming in,
我们需要稳定
we need stability.
是啊 或许你说得对
Yeah, yeah. You may be right.
我需要牺牲一个重量级的炮灰
I need one meaningful skull to wave.
如果股东大会是明天 那我们就输了
If the shareholders' meeting were tomorrow, we lose.
我需要说服几个大股东
I need to persuade a couple of big figures.
所以...
So...
有谁想说点什么吗
anyone like to say anything?
不管是谁 我都会照顾他的
I'll take care of whoever it is.
谁也不会被遗忘
No one will be forgotten.
好吧 我的意思是 我...如果我们要这样做
Well, I mean, I... If we're doing this,
我不想说屁话
I don't want to spread shit around.
我们都是忠实的仆人 但是 我...我只是说
We're all loyal servants, but, so, I... I only say
我没有预谋 大概 法律总顾问
without malice aforethought, presumably general counsel
是网络的中心 抱歉 格丽 我喜欢你的
is center of the web. Sorry, Gerri. I like you.
没有比格丽更忠诚的人了
There is no one more loyal than Gerri.
确实 那弗兰克呢
Exactly. What about Frank?
我的意思是 弗兰克今天怎么会在这里
I mean, how come Frank is even here today?
-谢谢  -别客气[欢迎你当炮灰]
‐Thank you. ‐You're welcome.
我看得出来 我接受
I could see it. I'd take it.
-选我有道理  -对吧
‐I make sense. ‐  Right?
他对你做了那件事 董事会政变
And after what he did to you, the boardroom coup?
-过去的事已经过去了  -对 在这种情况下...
‐Water under the bridge. ‐Right. In which case...
我想 在某种意义上
I guess, in a certain way,
我...我...对家人的轻率行为
my... my... indiscretion against the family,
我要客观地说
I would say objectively,
让我不那么容易做出牺牲
makes me less of a compelling sacrifice,
这是我唯一要说的 不像...比如
is the only thing I would say. Unlike... for instance...
卡尔这样忠诚的仆人
a loyal servant like Karl.
我...
I...
谢谢你 弗兰克 谢谢你的话...
Thank you, Frank, for that. ...
好吧 在我看来 如果瑞亚不再参与
Well, my thing, I guess, is that if, Rhea is no more,
可悲的是 我们又回到了...
sadly, we're back to having, ...
我们又回到格丽担当名义接班人的境地
we're back to Gerri as named successor.
所以 可以这么说 这让她变成了更容易被宰杀的肥猪
So, that fattens her up for the kill, so to speak.
我想每个人都知道我一直
I guess everyone knew I was always
只是纸上面的一个虚的名字 对吧
just a name on a piece of paper. Right?
我觉得你一直比一个虚的名字更重要
I think you were always more than that.
-我觉得那完全是...  -再加上...好吧 等等
-I think that's exactly... ‐And plus... well, hang on.
再加上 你知道吗 旧的习字本
Plus, you know, the old copy book
有点污点 费用账户
is a bit blotty. Expense accounts,
女儿们用公司的钱买头等舱
daughters first class on the company coin.
-说得"好" 卡尔  -是的
‐Right, Karl. ‐Y... Yeah.
"我只是去做运动按摩
"I just went for the sports massage.
我根本不知道是那种机构"
I had no idea it was that sort of establishment."
-好吧  ‐卡尔听上去是不错的人选
-Okay. ‐ Karl sounds good.
...香肠小偷
...Sausage thief.
你知道吗 理论上 选格丽很完美
You know, Gerri is theoretically kind of perfect.
说得好
Hear, hear.
不 "理论上"
No, "theoretically."
不 那是胡扯 我不同意
No, that's bullshit. I disagree.
-不  -为什么
‐No. ‐Why?
为什么我不同意吗 因为那是我的看法
Why do I disagree? Because that's my opinion.
好的 但是你的理由呢
Yeah, but your reasoning?
说真的 格丽 为游轮的事背锅
Seriously, Gerri? To pay for cruises?
我们...我们害死一个女性高层
We... We take out a senior woman?
我们难道不是已经 你们知道的
Haven't we, you know,
在这里开个玩笑 已经害死了足够多的女人了吗
kidding here, killed enough women already?
我的意思是 我觉得显而易见的选择是
I mean, I think the obvious choice is,
我讨厌这样说 因为他是个非常出色的人
and I hate to say it because he's such a swell guy,
是...
is...
汤姆
Tom.
-你说什么  -是的
-Excuse me? ‐Yeah.
对吧 我知道 但你知道吗 你是游轮部门负责人
Right? I know, but you know, head of cruises.
但是我...嗯...
But I... Well...
-我一直都是个忠心耿耿的仆人  -对 但是
‐I have been a loyal servant. ‐Yeah, but,
你知道吗 如果...如果这是...
you know, if... If this is...
在实验室 提取了人类的情感
just laboratory time, human emotions extracted,
汤姆 我他妈的爱你 老兄
Tom, I fucking love you, dude,
但是你在莫·莱斯特这事上搞砸了
but you shat the bed over Mo Lester.
但是我被安排上去就是为了当沙...
But I was sent in there as the beating...
就是为了当该死的沙包 我承受了各种殴打
as the fucking beating man. I took the beating.
你被艾维斯忽悠了
You got suckered in by Eavis.
-我回答了问题  ‐你不应该回答问题
‐I answered the questions. ‐You don't answer the questions.
你不应该回答问题
You don't answer the questions.
好的 这是 第一条规则
Okay, that's, like, rule one.
我...我不是在这里殴打你
I'm... I'm not beating up on you here.
我只是说 他赢了你
I'm just saying, he got a win off you
而你有点像是这事的主角 而且...
and you're kind of the face of this, and...
我不知道 听着 我这样说
I don't know. Look, I'm saying this,
但我不相信这些话 我只是...我这样说
but I don't believe it. I'm just... I'm saying it,
因为这是我们大家发言的时刻
because this is the time we're all saying things.
是的 我觉得汤姆可行 我觉得 算是一种澄清
Yeah, I think, Tom works. Just kind of a clarity, I think.
-是的  -你懂的
-Yeah. ‐ You know.
有人愿意谈谈我的优点吗
Anyone care to speak to my qualities?
‐不 汤姆听上去合乎逻辑  -什么
‐No, Tom looks logical. ‐What?
-游轮部门负责人 销毁文件  -什么
‐Cruises. Document destruction. ‐ What?
我并不是说应该这样
I'm not saying that it should be.
我的意思是 我...我是说 你就像家人
I mean, I... I'm saying, you're like family,
这很好 但也不是...家人 这样蛮好
which is good, but also not... family, which is kinda good.
汤姆 这很显而易见[房间里的大象] 可以这么说
Tom, it's the elephant in the room, we can say that.
不 不可以这么说 没必要说显而易见
No, we can't. There's no need to say the elephant in the room.
房间里还有其他15个人显而易见
There are 15 other elephants in the room.
汤姆 你的证词 你...
Tom, the testimony, you...
-你算是把自己变成靶子了  -为什么不应该是你
‐you kind of put a target on yourself. ‐ Why shouldn't it be you?
如果应该是我 为什么...为什么不应该是你
lf it should be me, why... why shouldn't it be you?
我不是在攻击你 而是在维护你
I'm not attacking you, I'm defending you.
好吧 感觉不像是在维护我 感觉不像是
Well, it doesn't feel like that. It doesn't feel like that.
好吧 很好 我当炮友怎么有用
Okay. Fine. How do I work?
我不知道 我不知道
I don't know! I don't know.
我只是...我不是在说你 我只是说
I'm just... I'm not saying you. I'm just saying.
我的意思是 我想如果我们要选小西
I mean, I guess if we were saying Shiv,
我们得强调骚扰证人这件事
we'd highlight witness tampering and,
你们知道的 她要接任 但是...
you know, that she was gonna take over, but...
我不知道 可能...可能不会有用
I don't know, it probably... it probably doesn't work.
是的 太正确了 不会他妈的有用
Yeah. Too right it doesn't fucking work.
选我没道理 我从没加入公司
I don't make sense. I've never been inside.
那他们两个一起呢 小西和汤姆
What about both of them? Shiv and Tom.
美女和野兽
Beauty and the beast.
牺牲汤姆有用吗
Does Tom work?
老实说 汤姆...
Honestly, Tom...
我觉得他的咖位还不够 没有冒犯的意思
I don't think he's a big enough skull. No offense.
那汤姆加上他妈的格雷格毛毛雨怎么样
Then how about Tom with some fucking Greg sprinkles?
什么 格雷格毛毛雨
What? Greg sprinkles?
是的 只是一个派对大礼包 你作为甜味剂
Yeah, just a party pack. You as a sweetener.
是的 是的
Yeah. Yeah.
二郎神和哮天犬 我开始明白了
Elmo and Big Bird, I could start to see that.
-然后 你再把卡尔 弗兰克 或者雷加进去  -好的
‐And then you throw in, like, a Karl, or a Frank, or a Ray. ‐  Okay.
-是啊 对 对 有什么不可以呢
‐Yeah, yeah. No, no. Why not?
我只是在举例而已
These are just examples.
对 当然 是的 对 继续
No, of course. Yeah, no, just go ahead,
不过是为你们服务了23年而已
worked for you for 23 years.
什么... 格雷格毛毛雨到底是什么
What... What precisely are Greg sprinkles?
基本上来说 格雷格毛毛雨是一个很棒的搭配
Greg sprinkles are basically a fantastic garnish
基本上对这个桌子上的任何人来说都是
to basically anyone seated at this table.
-好的  ‐就像汤姆圣代冰淇淋...
‐Okay. ‐Like a Tom sundae with a...
上面放着一点格雷格樱桃
with a little Greg cherry on top.
-完美  ‐不 我反对
‐ Perfect. ‐ No, I object.
我真的反对...我的意思是...
I really do. I... I mean...
-谁在乎你啊  ‐我不仅仅是毛毛雨
-Who cares? ‐I'm more than a sprinkle.
你知道吗 那你呢
You know? What about you?
‐选罗曼怎么样  -选我吗
‐What about Roman? ‐What about me?
我们来听听 说说你的理由
Let's hear it. What's the pitch?
大家都知道你是个糟糕的人
You're widely known as a horrible person.
谢谢 脚趾缝里的泥垢 你为什么不...
Thanks, toe jam, why don't you...
可以是罗曼
It could be Roman.
房间里还有头大象[还有个显而易见的人]
There's another elephant in the room.
如果我毛遂自荐牺牲自己呢
But what about I just throw myself over the side?
...没想到你会这样说
... Didn't see that coming.
是的 作为回报 给我一些经济补偿
Yeah, in return for a little payout.
我现在手头紧 就把我捆起来吧
I'm cash strapped, so just strap me
绑在甜美的金色降落伞上
into that sweet, sweet golden parachute
再把我扔进火山
and toss me in the volcano.
对不起 我只是看不到...我看不到怎么和你扯上关系
I'm sorry. I just don't... I don't see that.
听着 好吧 你们就说 你知道吗 是我在幕后操纵
Like, look, okay, you say, you know, eminence grise.
-什么  ‐所以 我是老黎塞留[法国的红衣主教 阴谋家]
‐What? ‐So, old Richelieu here,
在幕后鬼鬼祟祟
skulking around in the background,
这些年来一直在幕后操纵 谁知道呢
pulling the strings all these years. Who knew?
邪恶的影响者终于摆脱了
The maligned influencer finally rid of.
你 你真是太好心了 康纳
That's, that's kind of you, Con.
谢谢 而且...我们会牢记这一点的
Thank you. And... we'll bear it in mind.
是的 所以 我...
Yeah, so I...
我需要仔细考虑
I need to reflect.
我的意思是 我们有...
I mean, we've...
半个主意 但是...是的
half an idea, but... Yeah.
晚点再谈
Later?
什么...什么 我们有半个主意 半个主意是什么意思
What's... What? We have half an idea? What's a half an idea?
-肯 我能和你说句话吗  -当然可以
‐Ken. Can I get one word? ‐Yeah, sure.
什么事
What's up?
我们没事吧
Are we okay?
我告诉她 欢迎她 但是...
I told her she was welcome, but...
-她脾气很差  -嗯 我不知道 她...
‐she's on a hair trigger. ‐Yeah, I don't know. She...
她只是...我不知道
She just... I don't know.
斯图威有空吗
Is Stewy available?
好的...
Okay...
我觉得有 他在帕克索斯岛上 是的
I think so. He's on Paxos. Yeah.
和他谈可能会...很丢脸
It might be... humiliating.
嗯 当然
Yeah, sure.
但是 这是我应该做的 即使我不想做
But what I ought to do, I don't wanna do.
不 不要这个湾 我不喜欢
No, not this one. I don't like it.
你不喜欢这个湾吗 这个湾怎么了
You don't like it? What's wrong with this one?
-我可以看到海胆  - 得了吧 汤姆
-I can see a sea urchin. ‐ Come on! Tom!
下一个海湾 谢谢 朱利叶斯
Next cove, please, Julius.
有无数个海湾 我们找个完美的
There are infinite coves. Let's find the perfect one.
谢谢你见面 伙计
Thanks for meeting, man.
有请 有请 有请
Please. Please, please, please,
请进 请进 请进 先生
come, come, come, sir.
你好吗 先生 请坐
How are you, sir? Please, take a seat.
你们需要吃点什么吗
You guys need anything?
是的 别等我们了
Yeah, don't wait for us or anything.
我等了 但我真的很饿
I waited, but I was really hungry.
你们好吗 你们需要吃点什么吗
You guys good? You guys need anything?
也许一会吧
Maybe in a minute.
好吧...这样的
Well... look.
我们都知道...
We both know...
这是...这是把利刃
it's a... it's a knife's edge.
你可能会赢 我们可能会赢
You may have it. We may have it.
我们的代理顾问告诉我们 我们可能会赢
Our proxy advisors tell us we probably have it.
而且...
And...
爸
Dad?
你看起来流了不少汗 老兄
You look a little sweaty, dude.
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
所以 我来做个交易
So, I've come to make a deal.
这不是谈判 这是个大动作
This isn't a negotiation. It's a one‐bang,
最后一笔交易 而且很慷慨
final‐deal offer and it's generous.
所以...不要用计算器来侮辱我
So... don't insult me with a counter.
我这么说吧 我们吃点章鱼
I say this, we eat some octopi,
我们握手言和 怎么样
we shake hands. Okay?
好吧 我喜欢你的提议 我真的喜欢
Okay, I love that. I really do.
三个董事会席位 包括肯的席位
Three board seats, including Ken's.
白纸黑字写定
You get a codified say
你们来任命我们的下一任总裁
in the appointment of our next CEO.
我们移除毒丸计划
We remove our poison pill,
对和你们共同商定的条款进行战略评估
conduct a strategic review on terms co‐set with you,
驳回我们所有有关代理权之争的诉讼
dismiss all our litigation on the proxy battle.
甩掉游轮这个包袱 好吗
Spin off cruises. Okay?
不 我觉得那行不通
No, I don't think that works.
-你他妈这是什么意思  -废话
-The fuck do you mean? ‐Bullshit.
你他妈的傻吗
Are you fucking stupid?
你必须考虑这一点
You have to consider that.
你必须问桑迪
You have to ask Sandy.
-那是他妈的很好的交易  -这对我们不起作用 先生
‐That is a good fucking deal. ‐lt does not work for us, sir.
伙计 我的意思是...你他妈说真的吗
Dude. I mean, are... are you fucking for real?
我的意思是 你...你他妈的得让它起作用
I mean, you... you need to fucking make it work.
好吗 不然我他妈的会亲自毁了你
Okay? Or I will personally fucking destroy you.
-我会晚上来找你...  -肯 这没用
‐I will come to you at night... ‐ Ken, it does not work
-对于你...  -用一把他妈的剃须刀
‐for u... ‐...with a fucking razor blade
-然后我会把你他妈的鸡巴割掉  ‐把你他妈的鸡巴割掉
‐and I will cut your fucking dick off. ‐Fucking dick off.
-然后拿去喂...  -然后推进你的屁眼里
-And I will feed it... ‐And then push it up your cunt
直到大便从我的鼻孔里喷出来
until poo poo pops out of my nose hole.
伙计 没关系 这没有任何意义
Dude, it doesn't matter. It doesn't mean anything.
你可以威胁说 塞一百万根断鸡巴
You can threaten to stuff a million severed dicks
进我的阴囊里 但实际情况是
into my ball bag, but the actual fact is,
我们每天都在说服越来越多的股东
we're persuading more and more shareholders every day
说我们会为他们提供一个更好的机会
that we offer them just a slightly better chance
用他妈的他们的钱 为他们
for them to make a little bit more money
赚更多的钱 就这么简单
on their fucking dollar, and that's all that this is.
你想说话吗
You wanna talk?
我为什么要想说话
Why would I wanna talk?
好吧
Fine.
你他妈的...
You fucking...
你他妈的出卖我 小西
You fucking toasted me, Shiv.
你...你坑了我
You... You fried me.
汤姆...
Tom...
我必须做一个诚实的中间人
I have to be an honest broker.
为了救你 我不能表现得太自私
To save you, I can't be seen to be acting in self‐interest.
我在听证会之前得到的建议很垃圾 小西
I got shitty advice before the hearing, Shiv.
你知道吗 这一点我不知道
You know, I don't know about that.
我被晾在那里暴晒
I got hung out to dry.
我爱你
I love you.
很好 谢谢
Great. Thanks.
不爱吗
No?
我不知道 我爱你 我爱欢这块石头
I don't know. I love you. I love this rock.
再见 石头
Bye, rock.
你死定了 这有什么意义
You're dead. What does it mean?
我不会让你发生任何事情的
I won't let anything happen to you.
你告诉过我...
You told me...
你告诉我 你想要一个开放的关系...
You told me you wanted an open relationship...
在我们他妈的新婚之夜
on our fucking wedding night.
这...是...
Is... Y...
所以 你一直在为此烦恼吗
So, you've been stewing on that?
没错 是的
Well, yes.
实际上 一直在为此烦恼
I have been stewing on that, actually.
我不是...嬉皮士...小西
I'm not... a hippie... Shiv.
我不想...
I don't want...
把假鸡巴塞进我的...我不想...
to stuff a dildo up my... I don't want...
我不想玩3P
I don't want to do threesomes.
-好的  -在我们的新婚之夜这样做
‐Okay. ‐On our wedding night?
被迫...同意...
Shanghaied into a... into a...
开放式性自由交易协议
open‐borders free‐fuck trade deal.
那...
It...
-那只是一个想法  -好吧...
‐lt was just an idea. ‐Well...
在...在神圣的婚礼祭坛上 那就是个大问题
that's... that's a biggie just to throw in at the altar.
你懂吗  "我愿意 我愿意 但我可能也会要求”
You know? "I do. I do, but I do maybe also demand"
尝试别人的鸡鸡"
to gobble the odd side‐dick."
"尝试别人的鸡鸡”
"Gobble the odd side‐dick"?
我不觉得你所做的事很酷
I don't think it was cool what you did.
我只是...我想 你知道吗...
I just... I think, you know...
很多时候 如果我仔细想想
I think a lot of time, if I think about it,
我想 很多时候 我真的很不开心
I think a lot of time, I'm really pretty unhappy.
你在说什么
What are you saying?
我不知道
I don't know.
我爱你 我真的爱你 我只是...我想知道...
I love you, I do. I just... I wonder if...
我想知道 如果没有你...我的难过
I wonder if the sad I'd be... without you
会不会比和你在一起时少一些
would be less than the sad I get from being with you.
好吧 我很抱...我很...
Well, I'm s... I'm...
我很抱歉 汤姆
I'm sorry, Tom.
我会和洛根谈谈
I'll talk to Logan.
不
No.
我去和洛根谈谈
I'll talk to Logan.
没关系
It's fine.
我自己可以
I'm fine.
嘿
Hey.
你还好吗 汤姆
You okay, Tom?
搞他妈什么啊
What the fuck?
谢谢你 洛根
Thank you, Logan.
-汤姆  -谢谢你的鸡肉
-Tom? ‐Thank you for the chicken.
刚刚是搞什么鬼
What the fuck was that?
我...我不知道 我觉得...
I... I don't know. I think...
压力 影响到大家了 爸
it's getting to people, Dad. The tension.
他吃了我他妈的鸡肉
He ate my fucking chicken.
那 接下来呢
So, what next?
把他的鸡巴塞进我的土豆沙拉里吗
Stick his cock into my potato salad?
你...你在犹豫不决吗
You... You wavering?
文件和游轮
Documents and cruises.
也许...让汤姆背锅
Maybe... Tom.
格丽
Gerri.
或者用格雷格代替
Or Greg instead.
好的
Okay.
汤姆
Tom.
我会照顾他的
I'll take care of him.
他会翻供吗
Would he flip?
如果坐监的话
Prison time?
为什么不选...你知道的...我们讨论过的
Why not... you know... what we discussed?
肯可以的
Ken works.
他清楚整件事
He was across the whole thing.
这样我会心痛
It hurts.
这样也很有用
It plays.
很明显
Obviously.
我只是...
I just...
觉得 汤姆不应该这样的下场...
think that, Tom doesn't deserve it...
而且 外面的世界也不会接受他的背锅
and, it doesn't work for the rest of the world.
我不同意
I don't.
那...
So...
你怎么看
What do you think?
这是大家需要做出艰难选择的时刻
It's the sort of tough choice people need to be able to make.
那些职位非常高的人需要做出艰难的选择
People who would be very senior people.
我不能选择 爸
I can't choose, Dad.
不
No.
不能
只要不...
Just not...
只要不是汤姆
Just not Tom.
求你了 为了我
Please. For me.
嘿 爸
Hey, Dad.
嘿 儿子
Hey, son.
从今天早上起 我再也不能做这种事了
I can't do any more of that shit from this morning.
不 不 当然 肯定的
No. No, sure. I bet.
格雷格...
Greg...
汤姆
Tom...
不起作用 也不会叠加
Doesn't work. Won't add up.
对 不 我明白了
Right. No, I see that.
他们也不会接受我
And they won't accept me.
我明白了 明白了
I get it. I do.
你知道吗...
You know...
我和玛西娅以前经常朗读给对方听
Marcia and I used to read to each other.
我读过她的历史
I'd read her history.
你知道吗 斯宾格勒 吉本 大人物
You know, Spengler, Gibbon, the big boys.
嗯
Okay.
印加人
The Incas...
在严重的危机时期...
in times of terrible crisis...
会向太阳献祭一个孩子
would sacrifice a child to the sun.
我对她说 他们是一群他妈的野蛮人
I said to her they were a bunch of fucking savages.
她的问题是...
Her thing was...
你愿意牺牲多心爱的人...
what could you possibly kill that you love so much...
去换取太阳再次升起
it would make the sun rise again?
她这么说的
She said that.
好的
Okay.
我想她
I miss her.
没关系 爸 没关系的
It's okay, Dad. It's okay.
谢谢 谢谢你 儿子
Thank you. Thank you, son.
听证会...
The hearings...
你做得很好
you did so well.
但现在...
But now...
你是集团的脸面
you're the face.
你经历了整治阶段
You were across the clean‐up.
传媒上说得过去
The optics make sense.
而且还有...
And what's more...
我信任你
I trust you.
我信任你 以防万一情况反转或者...
I trust you in case it turns or...
-变得...不堪  -嗯 是的 不 我明白的
‐gets... nasty. ‐Yep. Yep. No, I get it.
所以...
So...
我们会举行一次新闻发布会
we'll set up a press conference.
然后...
And...
你会承认你知道一切
you'll admit that you knew everything
而你主导了那些遮掩行为
and that you directed the cover up,
而且...没有涉及到更高层的人
and... it went no higher.
-好的  -好吗
-Okay. ‐Okay?
喂 爸 我...
Hey, Dad, I...
只是出于好奇...
just out of interest...
你有没有想过我能做到
Did you ever think I could do it?
做什么
Do what?
掌舵吗
The top job?
我不知道 也许吧
I don't know. Maybe.
你可以说出来的
You can say.
我...嗯 你知道吗 我只是...
I... Well, you know, I just...
你知道吗 你很聪明 你很好 但是我...
You know, you're smart, you're good, but I...
我只是不知道
I just don't know.
什么 快说吧
What? Come on.
你不是杀手
You're not a killer.
你必须成为杀手
You have to be a killer.
但是...
But...
当下...
nowadays...
也许你做不到 我不知道
maybe you don't. I don't know.
好吗
Okay?
-我们没事吧 你没事吧  -嗯
‐Are we good? You good? ‐Yeah.
我活该
I deserve it.
也许是我活该
Maybe I deserve it.
‐不 儿子  ‐是的 活该这一切
‐No, son. ‐Yeah, for everything.
不不不 天哪 不
No, no, no. God, no.
钱给的多吗
It's good to pay?
那个男孩
The boy?
不...
Nah...
不 不 不 不 不是因为那个
Nah, nah, nah, nah. Not that.
无真人参与 你是最好的
NRPI. You're the best.
不要自责了
Don't beat yourself up.
无真人参与 你知道的 那...
No real person involved. You know, it's...
那没什么
it's nothing.
对
Right.
我们走吧
Shall we?
格丽 我们经历过成千上万件这样的事情...
Gerri, we've been on a million of these things...
这颜色不错
It's a nice color.
是的 我知道 真的是...
Yeah. I know, it's really...
我决定了
I've decided.
肯吗
Ken?
拜托 不是吧 爸 不要
Come on, really? Dad, no.
有...
There's...
为什么不选...
What about the...
这些混蛋...之一
one of the... shitfuckers?
嘿 没关系 伙计们 你们摆脱困境了
Hey, it's okay. Guys, you're off the hook.
你还好吗
You okay?
是的 我很好
Yeah. I'm good.
而且...只是...
And... is it just...
我不想无礼 只是他一个人吗
I don't want to be rude. Just him?
是的 还有其他附加的人吗...
Yeah, are there any additionals...
首先...第二个儿子...
First... Second‐born son...
承担你的责任 这样非常容易被大家接受
with your responsibilities, it will be a very simple sell.
罗曼...
Roman...
你会成为全权的首席运营官
you're taking over as full chief operating officer.
是啊 什么...他妈的...
Yeah? What with... fucking...
"谨慎队长"在背后垂帘听政吗
Captain Cautious back in the next room?
不 不 弗兰克要负责进行
No, no. Frank's gonna be responsible
游轮部门的整治 你一个人
for the cruises clean up. You're on your own.
独角戏
Solo.
你能搞定吗
Can you handle it?
好吧 是的
Well, yeah.
是的 爸 那...
Yeah, Dad, that's...
真的令人激动
really exciting.
不 罗曼 这很棒
No, Rome. It's great.
好了 伙计们 吃饭吧 这餐算我请
Okay, guys, eat up. This one's on me.
你没事吧 伙计
You okay, dude?
你知道吗 如果你需要上洗手间...
You know, if you need to use the bathroom...
你可以去上的
you can use the bathroom.
我不会跳出窗的
I'm not gonna jump out the window.
嗯 我要去上
Yeah, I'll go.
是的 我只是...
Yeah, I just...
不管真假 我对整件事深表歉意...
Just for what it's worth, I'm sorry about this whole....
我...我只是觉得你爸的做法太...
I... I just think what your dad's doing is...
‐总之 我很遗憾  -嗯 谢谢
‐Anyway, I'm sorry. ‐Yep. Thank you.
好的
Okay.
你还好吗 肯
You okay, Ken?
如果你需要的话 旁边有水
There's water by the side if you need it.
我会让他们问三个问题
I'm gonna let them hit like three questions
然后就结束 好吗
and then that's it. Okay?
你爸刚刚发信息来了 他在看
Your dad just texted. He's watching.
你还好吗
You okay?
是的
Yeah.
只是...只是吃不下饭
Just... just can't eat.
不
No.
没关系 小西
It's okay, Shiv.
没关系
It's okay.
必须这么做
It had to be done.
是的 可怜的家伙
Yeah. Poor bastard.
早上好
Good morning.
罗伊先生准备了一份声明想宣读
Mr. Roy has a prepared statement he'd like to read.
然后 他将回答几个提问 谢谢
And then, he'll take a few questions. Thank you.
早上好
Good morning.
在即将召开股东大会之前
I have an announcement to make...
我要宣布一份关于
about wrongdoing at Waystar Royco
韦斯达罗伊科集团的不道德行为的声明
in advance of the upcoming shareholder meeting.
我被要求解释
I have been asked to explain my own role
自己在公司的违法行为管理
in the managing of illegality at the firm
以及相关的掩饰行为中的角色
and associated cover ups.
有人建议 我是吸收公众的愤怒和担忧的
And it has been suggested I would be a suitable figure
比较合适的人选
to absorb the anger and concern.
但是...
But...
事实上 我父亲才是那个万恶的...
the truth is that my father is a malignant presence...
...土霸王和骗子...
...a bully, and a liar...
而且 多年来 他完全清楚地知道这些事件
and he was fully personally aware of these events
并且努力地遮盖和掩藏这些真相
for many years and made efforts to hide and cover up.
他对类似莱斯特·麦克林托克这样屡教不改的惯犯
He had a twisted sense of loyalty to bad actors
有一种扭曲的忠诚...
like Lester McClintock...
我操
Fuck me.
他无视流动工人 工会
And a disregard for the safety of migrant workers,
工会工人
non‐union and union workers
以及弱势的演员和游客的安全
and for vulnerable performers and guests.
我父亲密切注视着他整个帝国的
My father keeps a watchful eye over every inch
每一寸土地
of his whole empire,
如果没有他的明确批准
and the notion that he would have allowed
就想支付数百万美元的
millions of dollars in settlements
和解与赔偿 这样的想法简直是...
and compensation to be paid without his explicit approval...
异想天开
is utterly fanciful.
今天 我带来了我的记录副本...
I have with me, today, copies of records...
这上面有他的个人签字
that show his personal sign off.
我们这些执行了他的愿望的人
How much those of us who executed his wishes
应该承担多少责任 我们改日再清算
bear responsibility is for another day.
但我觉得...
But I think...
今天是他统治结束的日子
this is the day his reign ends.
我会提供文件 并且可以回答你们在未来几天内
I'll be providing the documents and can answer any questions
可能提出的任何问题 非常感谢大家
you may have in the coming days. Thank you very much.
罗伊先生
Mr. Roy!
你对这些罪行的受害者有什么话要说吗
Do you have anything to say to the victims of these crimes?
你父亲知道你今天要发表这份声明吗
Did your father know you were making this statement today?
-罗伊先生  -我操 我操 我操
‐Mr. Roy. ‐Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
ZIMUXIA.CN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠